DenysPotapov

developer

contact

+38 050 330-20-57 skype: denys.potapov

denys.potapov@gmail.com

skills

PHP, python, MySQL, JavaScript, HTML, SCSS

languages

bilingual Ukrainian/Russian intermediate English basic German

profile

I am a developer with over 9 years experience working on a variety of projects from conception to delivery. I am conversant in a wide range of technologies, now focused on web development (PHP, python), follow the latest industry trends with great interest (SCSS, HTML5). My approach is methodical but creative. I am comfortable working either independently or as part of a team.

education

2002–2008 M.Sc. degree in Computer Science NTUU 'KPI'

Specialisation in computer systems and robotics

experience

2012—Present barzo.com.ua founder

Creating and launching a start-up company. Developing from the ground e-commerce platform (PHP, MySql, HTML, SCSS). Managing

team of 3 freelancers.

2012—Present **Qport** project manager

Creating a large network of digital signage systems (biggest project with 8000 screens). Integrating ERPsystem in retail stores (15 stores).

2009—2012 **Qport** develope

Developing interactive screens software (python). Developing an ERP

system for retail stores (1c ERP).

2008—2009 **Physico-technological institute** Leading engineer

Development and integration of foundry process modeling system (Object Pascal) for perspective developments department institute of metals and alloys of the National academy of science of Ukraine

2005—2007 **Proling Office** developer

Development of machine translation system ProlingOffice (C#) and it's

online version (ASP.NET)

awards

August 2014 IQLab Challenge 2nd place

PHP backend development

November 2013 UA Web Challenge V 3rd place

Backend development

Codingame oDesk Contest 5th place

python developers

skills

basic **Objective-C, C++, Assembler**

intermediate JavaScript, HTML, SASS

advanced PHP, python, MySQL

languages

native Russian/Ukrainian

intermediate **English** conversationally fluent

basic German basic words and phrases only

interests

blogging habrahabr.ru

Top-150 author in biggest Russian-speaking IT community

volunteer Running a code club

Code-club in Kyiv is a part of network of volunteer-led after school cod-

ing clubs for children aged 9-11

running